[
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "something, better something than nothing?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "io, pli bona io ol nenio",
    "score": 0,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "some kind, it is some kind of language?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "ia, gxi estas ia lingvo",
    "score": 0,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "some time, I some time beat him?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "iam, mi iam venkis lin",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "then (time), but not before then?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "tiam, sed ne pli frue ol tiam",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "that, what does that mean?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "tio, kion tio signifas",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "what, what are you reading?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "kio, kion vi legas",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "someone, someone was here?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "iu, iu estis cxi tie",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "nothing, nothing scares me?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "nenio, nenio timigas min",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "always, I always am with you?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "cxiam, mi cxiam estas kun vi",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "that kind, I hate that kind of weather?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "tia, mi malamas tian veteron",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "all, not all that glitters is gold?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "cxio, ne cxio brilanta estas oro",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "what kind, what kind of plant do they grow?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "kia, kian planton ili kreskas",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "that one, I already know that one?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "tiu, mi jam konas tiun",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "never, only that one doesn't fail, who never does, better late than never?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "neniam, nur tiu ne eraras, kiu neniam ion faras, pli bone malfrue ol neniam",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "every, every man is mortal?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "cxiu, cxiu homo estas mortema",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "no one, no one knows where he lives?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "neniu, neniu scias kie li logxas",
    "score": 1,
    "previous_raise": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "who, to who are you speaking?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "kiu, al kiu vi parolas",
    "score": 2,
    "previous_raise": 2
  },
  {
    "type": "atomic",
    "question": "when, when does it start?",
    "note": null,
    "answer": "kiam, kiam gxi komencigxis",
    "score": 2,
    "previous_raise": 2
  }
]
